let STORE = {
    questions: [
    {//1
    question: 'Which of these is NOT a strain of Coronavirus?',
    options: ['SARS', 'MERS', 'T-VIRUS', 'COVID-19'],
    answer: 'T-VIRUS'
    },
    {//2
    question: 'What does "Corona" mean in latin?',
    options: ['Beer', 'Crown', 'Tyrant', 'Hat'],
    answer: 'Crown'
    },
    {//3
    question: 'Coronavirus typicaly affects which part of the human body?',
    options: ['Upper respiratory system', 'Intestinal tract', 'Sinuses', 'The brain'],
    answer: 'Upper respiratory system'
    },
    {//4
    question: 'Which of these animals have we NOT found to carry a strain of Coronavirus',
    options: ['Alpacas', 'Bats', 'Pigs', 'Alligators'],
    answer: 'Alligators'
    },
    {//5
    question: 'COVID-19 is currently thought to have originated from which of these animals?',
    options: ['Alpacas', 'Bats', 'Pigs', 'Alligators'],
    answer: 'Bats'
    },
    {//6
    question: 'Covid-19 is though to have originated from which region?',
    options: ['Raccoon City', 'Cairo, Egypt', 'Wuhan, China', 'Venice, Italy'],
    answer: "Wuhan, China"
    },
    {//7
    question: 'Which of these things should you NOT be doing during the current COVID-19 outbreak?',
    options: ['Wash your hands', 'Social Distancing', 
    'Travel to other countries', 'Buy mass quantities of toilet paper'],
    answer: 'Travel to other countries'
    },
    {//8
    question: 'Who is the most at risk during this time?',
    options: ['The elderly', 'People with auto-immune disorders', 
    'People with pre-existing respiratory disorders', 'All of the above'],
    answer: 'All of the above'
    },
    {//9
    question: 'Why is it important to practice social distancing at this time?',
    options: ['To keep those at risk from catching COVID-19',
     'To finish off your backlog of video games', 
     'To help sread COVID-19', 
     'To keep Umbrella Corp from running tests on you'],
    answer: 'To keep those at risk from catching COVID-19'
    },
    {//10
    question: 'Is there a cure for COVID-19 at this time',
    options: ['No', 'Yes'],
    answer: 'No'
    }
],
};